Hey, I'm Amanda Seals. Come take a ride with me through how you get blocked.
So this is Madeleine Elaine. Hey, Maddie. Now, Madeleine Elaine disagreed with me about my take
on Trump's level of importance in the Epstein files. She begins, least important aspect of the
files. I disagree. No problem. I don't think he's the most important, but to say he's the least
important as he stands as the leader of the free world, you know, she is completely in her right
to have her own opinion. Here's where things go left. She adds, come on, boo-boo. Seems important
to me. This is the internet reflex that so many folks cannot seem to stop themselves from succumbing
to. The necessity to be sassy. The necessity to be snide. You could have just respectfully disagreed
with me and kept on with your life, white lady. But instead, you felt the need to try to insult
my intelligence. Boo-boo, you must think I'm boo-boo the fool. You have to don't even know
who boo-boo the fool is, right? Get your ass out there on the front line and stay focused
and out of my comments. You're damn rude, eh?